♪ She take my money well I'm in need ♪
♪ Yeah she's a triflin' friend indeed ♪
♪ Oh she's a gold digger ♪
♪ Way over town that digs on me ♪
♪ She give me money now I ain't
sayin' she a gold digger ♪
♪ When I'm in need but she ain't messin' ♪
♪ with no broke broke ♪
♪ She give me money now I ain't
sayin' she a gold digger ♪
♪ When I'm in need but she ain't messin' ♪
♪ With no broke broke ♪
♪ I gotta leave get down
girl go 'head get down ♪
♪ I'm gonna leave get down
♪ I gotta leave get down
girl go 'head get down ♪
♪ I gotta leave get down girl go 'head ♪
♪ Cutie the bomb met
her at a beauty salon ♪
♪ With a baby Louis Vuitton
under her underarm ♪
♪ She said I can tell you rock
I can tell by your charm ♪
♪ Far as girls you got a flock ♪
♪ I can tell by your charm and your arm ♪
♪ But I'm lookin' for the
one have you seen her ♪
♪ My psychic told me she'll
have a (muted) like Serena ♪
♪ Trina Jennifer Lopez four kids ♪
♪ And I gotta take all they
bad (muted) to show biz ♪
♪ Okay get your kids but
then they got their friends ♪
♪ I pulled up in the
Benz they all got up in ♪
♪ We all went to din'
and then I had to pay ♪
♪ If you (muted) with this
girl then you better be paid ♪
♪ You know why ♪
♪ It take too much to touch her ♪
♪ From what I heard she
got a baby by Busta ♪
♪ My best friend said she
used to (muted) with Usher ♪
♪ I don't care what none of
y'all say I still love her ♪
♪ She give me money now I ain't
sayin' she a gold digger ♪
♪ When I'm in need but she ain't messin' ♪
♪ With no broke broke ♪
♪ She give me money now I ain't
sayin' she a gold digger ♪
♪ When I'm in need but she ain't messin' ♪
♪ With no broke broke ♪
♪ I gotta leave get down
girl go 'head get down ♪
♪ I gotta leave et down girl go 'head ♪
♪ Eighteen years eighteen years ♪
♪ She got one of your kids
got you for eighteen years ♪
♪ I know somebody payin' child
support for one of his kids ♪
♪ His baby mama car and
crib is bigger than his ♪
♪ You will see him on
TV any given Sunday ♪
♪ Win the Super Bowl and
drive off in a Hyundai ♪
♪ She was supposed to buy your
shorty Tyco with your money ♪
♪ She went to the doctor
got lipo with your money ♪
♪ She walkin' around lookin'
like Michael with your money ♪
♪ Should've got that insured
Geico for your money money ♪
♪ If you ain't no punk
holler we want prenup ♪
♪ We want prenup yeah ♪
♪ It's somethin' that you need to have ♪
♪ 'Cause when she leave yo' (muted) ♪
♪ She gon' leave with half ♪
♪ Eighteen years eighteen years ♪
♪ And on the 18th birthday
he found out it wasn't his ♪
♪ She give me money now I ain't
sayin' she a gold digger ♪
♪ When I'm in need but she ain't messin' ♪
♪ With no broke broke ♪
♪ She give me money now I ain't
sayin' she a gold digger ♪
♪ When I'm in need but she ain't messin' ♪
♪ With no broke broke ♪
♪ I gotta leave get down
girl go 'head get down ♪
♪ I gotta leave get down girl go 'head ♪
♪ Now I ain't sayin' you a
gold digger you got needs ♪
♪ You don't want a dude to
smoke but he can't buy (muted) ♪
♪ You go out to eat he can't
pay y'all can't leave ♪
♪ There's dishes in the back
you gotta roll up his sleeves ♪
♪ But while y'all washin' watch him ♪
♪ He gon' make it to a
Benz out of that Datsun ♪
♪ He got that ambition
baby look at his eyes ♪
♪ This week he moppin' floors
next week it's the fries ♪
♪ So stick by his side ♪
♪ I know there's dudes ballin'
and yeah, that's nice ♪
♪ And they gonna keep callin' and tryin' ♪
♪ But you stay right girl ♪
♪ And when you get on
he'll leave yo' (muted) ♪
♪ For a white girl ♪
♪ I gotta leave get down
girl go 'head get down ♪
♪ I gotta leave get down girl go 'head ♪
♪ Let me hear that back ♪